Guide to the Scott Hubbard Papers SC1286
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Scott Hubbard Papers
1972-2016
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Hubbard, Scott, 1948-
SC1286
197 gigabyte(s)
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Scott Hubbard, 2016-2017.
Hubbard, Scott, 1948-; Hubbard, Scott, 1948-; National Aeronautics and Space Administration; Stanford University. Department of Aeronautics and Astronautics. Faculty; Challenger (spacecraft).
- Challenger Accident Investigation Board Materials, Accession ARCH-2017-019
  Scope and Contents
  Materials in this series are related to Hubbard's work on the Columbia Accident Investigation Board (CAIB). The CAIB was organized by NASA to investigate the Space Shuttle Columbia in 2003, and released its final report on August 26, 2003.
  - Final Report/CAIB, 2003 Jun 16 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CAIB Report Review Material Chapters 5 to 9, 2003 Aug 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Unlabeled (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bookshelf history (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Log in material (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Group 3/ final rep't hubbard, 2003 May (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cab/ NASA update, 2003 Aug 26 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - RTF Impl plan, 2003 Aug 31 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Articles, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Unlabeled, 2003 Jun-Jul (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Impact test update, 2003 Jun 12 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CAIB final push (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - impact tests (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Test results fiberglass (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Press tellcon, 2003 Jun 4 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CAIB (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - meeting calendar and summaries, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Presentations, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Notes (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - RCC test, 2003 Jun 5 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Next impact test (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Pics (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Group 3 pres, 2003 Apr 16 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - TPS analysis (tiles, RCC, flexible) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Hearing/press conf. congress mat'l (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - OEX review, 2003 Mar 25 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Addn'l personnel (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Crater (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Health Mg't (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Photo/TV analysis (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Gehman Sensitive memos (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Interim Recc's CAIB (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Return to flight, 2003 Apr 15 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Allen Flynt (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Move to D.C. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Presentations, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Presentations, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Shuttle ground operations, 2003 Feb 12 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Solid Rocket Booster, 2003 Feb 13 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Operational experience with hypersonic flight, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - MRT summary, 2003 Feb 14 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Unlabeled (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Unlabeled (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Columbia Accident Investigation Board, 2003 Feb 15 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - ET Foam #3, 2003 Apr (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ET foam Count'd (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ET foam-tps story, 2003 Feb (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - RCC Panel 6 test readiness review (TRR), 2003 May 22 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Impact analysis schedule (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Foam impact tests (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - CAIB background, 2003 Feb (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - CAIB data (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Foam impact test 2, 2003 Mar (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Foam impact test 3, 2003 Apr (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - STS background (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - CAIB/OSC briefings, 2003 Feb (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Other mishap reports, 2000 Mar (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Promotional material, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Space exploration initiative, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Ames Research Center, 1998-2003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ames Research Center, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - NASA folder (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Aviation week, 1996 Jan 22-29 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - NASA folder (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Astrogram, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - LP press conference, 1998 Mar (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Neurolab, 1998 Apr 17 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Ky Av Hall of Fame, 1998 Jan (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Lightner museum (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - The Ames Astrogram, 1998 Mar 6 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Magazine launch, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper, 2003 Apr-Jul (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - STS 107, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Papers (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Magazines, 2003 Sep-Nov (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Presentations (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Columbia Accident Investigation Board Morning News Clips, 2003 Mar-Jun (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 2003 Mar (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Articles, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Presentations (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - HP/Computer pamphlets (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Morning news clips correspondence, 2003 Feb-Mar (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Columbia Accident Investigation Board News clips, 2003 Feb-Mar (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - CAIB Agency Wide Action Matrix, 2003 Nov 7 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - FY progress report, 1982 Nov (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - NASA Photographs (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Presentations (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Presentations (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - SRB presentations (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 2003 May (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Orbiter, 1989-1999 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Director's Envelope, 2002 Sep 19-2005 Jan 27 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Director's Envelope, 2002 Sep 19-2005 Jan 27 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - The Ames Astrogram (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - NASA correspondence (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Popular Science, 1998 Dec (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Newspapers (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Trellis Art Photograph (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - LP misc keepsake, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Photograph (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Vanderbilt magazine, SF opera guild, 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - CAIB/ group 3 to SwRI, 2003 Mar 4 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Top Shelf (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Second Shelf (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Presentation Slideshow, 2003 May (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Impact Bfg, 2003 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Final Report/CAIB (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - PAO Material, 2003 Feb (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - CAIB-Press, 2003 Feb 24 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - CAIB PAO, 2003 Mar (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Press conference, 2003 Apr 15 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Return to flight, 2003 Apr 15 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Book shelf CAIB Admin, 2003 Mar (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Group 3 Admin (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Debris Analysis, 2003 Mar 25 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - "Follow the TPS"-Arnord (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Group 4 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Scenarios, 2003 Mar 6 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Scenarios, 2003 Mar 26 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - STS 107 board/older papers, 2003 Feb 8 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Columbia Accident Investigation Board, 2003 Feb (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Unlabeled (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Presentations 1 of 2, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Presentations 2 of 2, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 2003 May 23 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Presentations 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Presentations 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - NASA oxidation of reinforced carbon-carbon subjected…, 2000 Mar (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - NASA, 1993 May 10 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Presentations (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 2003 Mar (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Scott-press package (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - FFRDC FRC, 2004 Dec (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Competed vs Direct, 2004 Jun (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - FRC-next (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - UC, 2005 Feb (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Nomet, 2005 Jan (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - UARC, 2004 Dec (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Zann G., 2007 Feb 7 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Talks/pres, 2003 Dec (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Astronaut remembrance (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Talks/pres (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - NASA folder (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - All hands KARC, 2004 Nov (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - LANL, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NAI/ ABSICON (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - CAIB @ IAF, 2004 Mar 11 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - LLNL, 2004 Feb (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Boot Camp (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Stats, 2004 May 24 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - WARC (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Ames family, 2004 Dec 10 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Ames Center overview, 2004 Nov 18 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Saudia-Livermore (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - BASIC (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Ames Current (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Lunar exp. science, 2006 Jul (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Life in the Univ. new vision, 2006 May 10 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - NASA science plan, 2006 Jun 23 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - NASA budget, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - CSC-rollout (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Future Business contacts, 2006 Sep (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Entrepeneurs (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Entrep. Space next steps (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - presentations, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Biology, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - CSA presentation (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - CSA conference, 2006 Nov 30-Dec 1 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Freund-earthquake, 2007 Feb (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Cots, 2006 Jul (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - photographs (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - space portal (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - AIAA (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - 2nd shelf pile (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - CAIB (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - STS 107 presentation, 2003 Feb 20 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Notebook (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Aerospace Safety Advisory Panel Annual Report, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - ESAS, 2004 Oct (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Life in the Universe, SS, Earth (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CAIB Report Review Material Chapters 5 to 9, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Final scenarios, 2003 Apr (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Presentation slideshows (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Paper, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Stickers and buttons (Box 7)
  - Proceedings Nasa Workshop, 2000 Mar 6-7; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - A Columbia Theory P. Curto, 2003 Mar 20; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Columbia Web Site Archive, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-249
  - Slides
    - AIAA paper (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Astrobiology (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Galileo (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - IE3 talk (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - IE3 dislocation study, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - LP talk (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - LP talk - final (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Lunar prospector (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Space statiion (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - unlabeled (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Audiovisual Material
    - SONY Alpha Particle Disk From Nick Wright, 8_01 (Box 8)
    - EWIFS Stuff from SBRC, 8_02 (Box 8)
    - Backup Logons, 8_03 (Box 8)
    - Diaz, 8_04 (Box 8)
    - Lunar Prospector GRS simulated and spectrum, 8_05 (Box 8)
    - Scott Hubbard Mcic II fx Dir retrospect backup, 1995 Jan 4; 8_06 (Box 8)
    - CP, 8_07 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous - Chuck's archives, more, Mac Terminal, 8_08 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous II - Microsoft chart, Versaterm, biohex to Unix, Mac Schedule, 8_09 (Box 8)
    - unlabeled, 8_10 (Box 8)
    - unlabeled, 8_11 (Box 8)
    - unlabeled, 8_12 (Box 8)
    - unlabeled, 8_13 (Box 8)
    - Presentation to kM AMES MARS project activities, 1994 Jun 24; 8_14 (Box 8)
    - TNS paper Si(Li), 1993; 8_15 (Box 8)
    - Code SF Projects, 8_16 (Box 8)
    - NSS, 1993; 8_17 (Box 8)
    - MESUR RTOP Corres, 1988; 8_18 (Box 8)
    - unlabeled, 8_19 (Box 8)
    - OAST ITP, 1991 Oct; 8_20 (Box 8)
    - unlabeled, 8_21 (Box 8)
    - unlabeled, 8_22 (Box 8)
    - Codes, AMES file storage, info tech, mgt. 1 admin, 8_23 (Box 8)
    - AMES Endura Attach., 2001; 8_24 (Box 8)
    - Generations packages 1. CTC version 2. full version, 2001 Jul; 8_25 (Box 8)
    - Mgmt/Adsten, 8_26 (Box 8)
    - unlabeled, 8_27 (Box 8)
    - Current Peggy Hot Topics AMES, 8_28 (Box 8)
    - Hot Topics zip disk AMES, 8_29 (Box 8)
    - pictures, 8_30 (Box 8)
    - Hot Topics disk 3, 8_31 (Box 8)
    - Endora Attach, 8_32 (Box 8)
    - Gate to Gate, 8_33 (Box 8)
    - Hot Topics #1, 8_34 (Box 8)
    - MESUR/SSAAC Report V. Fig, TAB, PM VI. PM VII. PM, Text, VIII PM, FIG, TAB, 8_35 (Box 8)
    - MESUR/SSAAC Report VI Fig, Tab, 8_36 (Box 8)
    - MESUR Interim QA Report Section IV 1 of 2, 8_37 (Box 8)
    - MESUR Interim QA Report Section IV 2 of 2, 8_38 (Box 8)
    - Hot Topics #2, 8_39 (Box 8)
    - Earth Science Division Annual reports, 1999-2000; 8_40 (Box 8)
    - Earth Science Division Annual Report, 2001; 8_41 (Box 8)
    - NASA Center for Computational Astrobiology and Fundamental Biology Annual Report, 2001; 8_42 (Box 8)
    - Kovacs In Situ Mars B10, 2002 Feb 12; 8_43 (Box 8)
    - ARC -L3rev3.ppt, 8_44 (Box 8)
    - Michael L. Hinas @ NASA.gov FF Heavy Spacecraft Concept Movie RogerArno@comcast.net, 2003 May 29; 8_45 (Box 8)
    - Nanotechnology at Ames Research Center Presentation to Code S, 2002 Dec 4; 8_46 (Box 8)
    - Second Technical interchange Meeting Final Presentations, 2002 Aug 27-28; 8_47 (Box 8)
    - Presentations - linked, 8_48 (Box 8)
    - Staubach Visit, 8_49 (Box 8)
    - Presentations w/ ATM Movie, 8_50 (Box 8)
    - ATM - OK, 8_51 (Box 8)
    - The Search for Life on Mars following the Water, 1995-1997; 8_52 (Box 8)
    - STAIF Talk, 8_53 (Box 8)
    - The Search for Life on Mars: Follow the Water presentation, 8_54 (Box 8)
    - Hubbard Computer Backup #1, 8_55 (Box 8)
    - Hubbard Computer Backup #2, 8_56 (Box 8)
    - Rocketcam Greatest Hits, 1997-2005; 8_57 (Box 8)
    - MESOR/SSAAC Report III. Firgures Tables, 8_58 (Box 8)
    - Si(Li) IEEE paper Disk 2 of 2, 1991 Nov 20; 8_59 (Box 8)
    - Si(Li) IEEE paper disk 1 of 2, 1991 Nov 20; 8_60 (Box 8)
    - MESUR SSAAC I, II, III (TOC, FOR, ACK, Cont, COVER), 8_61 (Box 8)
    - MESUR Monthly Reports, 8_62 (Box 8)
    - MESUR SSAAC V. Fig, tab, PM, Vi. PM, VII. PM, text, VIII. PM, Fig, TAB, 8_63 (Box 8)
    - MacEnvy, 8_64 (Box 8)
    - FY 1992 Proposal for the Advanced Planetary mission studies - H.Q. 1. Mesur 2. Neptune 3. Venus, 8_65 (Box 8)
    - MESUR/SSAAC Report Toc, For, ACK. Cont. I. PM, TAB, FIG II. PM, TAB, FIG III PM Cover sheet, 8_66 (Box 8)
    - 186-58-00 Proposal, 1992; 8_67 (Box 8)
    - Lunar workshop Text + figures, 1992 February; 8_68 (Box 8)
    - A Mars Environmental Survey Mission Concept AIAA - Williamsburgh, VA, 1991 Jul 17-19; 8_69 (Box 8)
    - MESUR SSAAC VI. Gif + Tab, 8_70 (Box 8)
    - World Program backup, 8_71 (Box 8)
    - MESUR Donald Ting, 8_72 (Box 8)
    - MESUR Donald Ting, 1991 Jun 11; 8_73 (Box 8)
    - unlabeled, 8_74 (Box 8)
    - unlabeled, 8_75 (Box 8)
    - Serial #14877, 8_76 (Box 8)
    - The Norton Utilities for the Macintosh Emergency Disk, 8_77 (Box 8)
    - Connect Grammar, 8_78 (Box 8)
    - Smartform Assistant, 8_79 (Box 8)
    - Word 5.0, 8_80 (Box 8)
    - Endura Attach., 8_81 (Box 8)
    - SSAAC IV 1 of 2, 8_82 (Box 8)
    - planetary Instrument cost workshop notes, 8_83 (Box 8)
    - Project charts -IR lab (piat files) Mar Explorer (PM, McDraft) Si(Li) (PM, Eps), 1992 Mar 26; 8_84 (Box 8)
    - Project chart -AUAP (PMm, TIFFGP3. EPS), 1992 Mar 26; 8_85 (Box 8)
    - 3-D Mission (Vertical) Page maker Mission on a page, 8_86 (Box 8)
    - Training cancellations, 1992 Feb 13; 8_87 (Box 8)
    - MESUR SSAAC III. Figures + Tables, 8_88 (Box 8)
    - MESUR SSAAC Section IV 2 of 2, 8_89 (Box 8)
    - Pyroelectric Detector development for the radiation measurement system, 1993 Jan 17-22; 8_90 (Box 8)
    - MESUR (misc), 8_91 (Box 8)
    - Research + Technology report inputs by G. Scott Hubbard, 1991; 8_92 (Box 8)
    - VMS NASA Columbia Press Conference, 11_01 (Box 11)
    - VMS NASA Columbia Press Conference, 11_02 (Box 11)
    - Columbia Accident Board- Scott Hubbard, 11_03 (Box 11)
    - Columbia Press Conference/Scott Hubbard, 11_04 (Box 11)
    - Columbia Accident Board -Scott Hubbard, 11_05 (Box 11)
    - Columbia Accident Board-Scott Hubbard, 2003 Feb 26; 11_06 (Box 11)
    - Kron 4 "Debris Recovery", 2003 Feb 25; 11_07 (Box 11)
    - Seconds from Disaster Columbia's Last Flight, 11_08 (Box 11)
    - Lubar Prospector Water on the Moon, 11_09 (Box 11)
    - Kentucky Press Coverage (Edited) - Master Copy, 11_10 (Box 11)
    - Extreme Machines, 11_11 (Box 11)
    - unlabeled, 11_12 (Box 11)
    - NASA Mars Science Update Work in Progress, not for Release Mars '03 Mission Announcement Mars Global Surveyor, 2000 Jul 27; 11_13 (Box 11)
    - Astrobiology News Conference, 1999 May 18; 11_14 (Box 11)
    - Lunar Prospector, 11_15 (Box 11)
    - Aeroassist Flight Experiment Aug. 91 Status, 1991 Aug; 11_16 (Box 11)
    - SAGAN, 11_17 (Box 11)
    - Moon Formation Beng + Cameron Mercury Mantle Beng, 11_18 (Box 11)
    - JPL AVC-96-136 Mars Pathfinder Animation 7:57, 24_01 (Box 24)
    - The Next 100 Years The Premier Global Event for the Centennial Flight, 2003 Jul 14-17; 24_02 (Box 24)
    - WARC 1. What's Cool 2. Reff in G, 24_03 (Box 24)
    - NASA Solutions: Sharing Aesospace Technology with America, 24_04 (Box 24)
    - "Scott Hubbard of NASA" BBC World News KQED-FM SF2007 Mar 12, 24_05 (Box 24)
    - NASA Lunar Prospector Mission, 24_06 (Box 24)
    - Columbia Accident investigation Board: Photo Archive, 24_07 (Box 24)
    - Forum: Ice on the Moon KQED-FM, 1996 Dec 5; 24_08 (Box 24)
  - PIX, 2002 Sep 27 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Speeches and Misc. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Kentucky Derby, Aviation, Aerospace magazine, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Intel, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - U. C. Santa Cruz in Memoriam: Denice Dee Denton, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Canberra Promo Literature (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - F. S. Goulding (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Publicity, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ASPR (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Science Digest, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Momentos, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Many extra copies of press release for Dept. Telescope (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Photo order form (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - speaking photos (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - LP momentos, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Misc., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lockheed Martin folder, 1997 Oct 8 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Misc. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Lockheed Martin folder, 1997 Oct 8 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - NASA folder (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - NASA folder, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - AIAA, 2000 Jan (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - SETI Institute Conversations with the Future (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - photographs (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Standard Paper Samples (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Astrogram, Aviation Week magazines, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Mars landing, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Spirit, Los Alamos, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - UCSC (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Marriott folder (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Travel guides (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Edinburgh travel, programs (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - newspapers, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Aerospace America, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Scientific American, Newsweek magazines, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - The Planetary Report, Final Frontier, California Wild magazines, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Misc. programs, NASA Awards, Goddard Memorial Dinner, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - NASA folder, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - NASA, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - JPL telephone directory, 1994 Jan (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - LMSC Talk, 1995 Mar 2 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - San Francisco, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Astrogram, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Misc, magazines, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Astrogram, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - NASA Space Projects Division, 1996 April (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - newspapers, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - newspapers, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NASA folder, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - NASA folder, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - LMLV Lockheed Martin folder (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - LP SES, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - PIX (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Newsweek, Electronic Business Today magazines, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Aviation Week Magazine, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - AD Astra magazine, 1995 May-Jun (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Astrogram, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Astrobiology Life in the Universe (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Letters from Courier Journal Article (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - newspapers, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The AMES Astrogram, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Aviation Week Magazine, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Newsweek, magazines, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Lunar prospector, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Misc., news clippings, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Aviation Week magazine, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Newspapers, Astrogram, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Photographs (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Lunar prospector, misc., 1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Newsweek magazine, 2000 Jan (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Lunar Prospector scale model kit (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Lunar Prospector, 1996 Jul (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Space Projects Record, 1990-1996 May (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Detector Meetings, 1992 Jan 23 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Space Directorate Record Staff Meetings, 1996 Apr (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - i-Gate Innovation for Green Advanced Transportation Excellence National Energy Systems Technology (NEST) Incubator Board of Director's Handbook binder contents, 2010 Nov 18 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Committee to Assess Solar System Exploration Meeting 2 binder contents, 2007 Mar 26-28 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Committee to Assess Solar System Exploration Meeting 1 binder contents, 2007 Feb 22-24 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mars Exploration Rover Project Preliminary Design Review/Flight System Preliminary Design Review Day 2, 2000 Oct 17-19 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Mars Exploration Rover Project Preliminary Design Review/Flight System Preliminary Design Review Day 3, 2000 Oct 17-19 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - MART Meeting #1, 2009 Apr 16-17 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Mars Exploration 1st Annual report to the Associate Administrator, 2001 Jul 13 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Mars Exploration Program A Presentation to the Mars Exploration Review Team (MERT), 2002 Apr 23-24 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mars Exploration Program A Presentation to the Mars Exploration Review Team (MERT), 2002 Aug 8-9 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Mars Exploration Rover Project Preliminary Design Review/Flight System Preliminary Design Review Day 1, 2000 Oct 17-19 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Mars Exploration Payload Analysis Group (MEPAG) Meeting Minutes and Viewgraphs, 2000 Nov 15-17 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Mars Exploration Program Assessment Group (MEPAG) Meeting Viewgraphs, 2000 Aug 8-10 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - NASA Ames Research Center Test Readiness Review, 1996 Nov 18-19 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - CRAF Tirex (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - SUN-Earth Connection Roadmap Strategic Planning for 2000-2025 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Astrometric Telescopic Facility: Preliminary Systems Definition Study Volume II: Technical Description, 1987 May (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 48th IAF Congress, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Origins the Fourth Annual State-of-origins Report, 2000 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - SMART Mission Concept Review Ames Research Center, 2010 Apr 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Proposals -PASCAL, Long days drive (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - NAI, AB Charts (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Pathfinder SWG's (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Old ARC presentations, VG's, Data Sheets (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - CAIB, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - CAIB Background, press (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - CAIB background, press materials (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - CAIB background, press (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mars Exploration Program transparencies (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - SFI Project Charts (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Lunar Prospector (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - LP Beyond, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - The Mars Environmental Survey (MESUR) Surface Lander Investigation of Mars (SLIM) Mission Overview, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - SFI Presentations (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Extraterrestrial Caves: Science, Habitat and Resources, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - SPEED: Small Payload Express Earth Day Delivery, 2004 Oct 11 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Blue Ribbon Task force Nanotechnology NASA Ames Research Center, 2004 Dec 17 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Federal Aviation Administration Center of Excellence for Commercial Space Transportation Year 4 Annual Report Executive Summary, 2014 Dec 31 (Box 10, Folder 1)